Guide to the Western Filmscript Collection
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Western Filmscripts Acquired After July 1996, 1917-2008
  - Gordon of Ghost City! [Chapter Seven: Entombed in the Tunnel], [1933] (Box 86)
  - Gordon of Ghost City! [Chapter Nine: Flames of Fury], [1933] (Box 86)
  - Gordon of Ghost City! [Chapter Eight: The Thundering Herd], [1933] (Box 86)
  - Gordon of Ghost City! [Chapter Ten: Swimming the Torrent], [1933] (Box 86)
  - Gordon of Ghost City! [Chapter Eleven: A Wild Ride], [1933] (Box 86)
  - Gordon of Ghost City! [Chapter Twelve: Mystery of Ghost City], [1933] (Box 86)
  - The Great Bank Robbery, 1967 June 15 (Box 87)
  - The Great Bank Robbery, 1968 April 10 (Box 87)
  - The Great Bank Robbery, 1968 August 26 (Box 87)
  - The Great Man's Lady, [circa 1942] (Box 87)
  - The Great Scout and Cat-House Thursday, 1975 September 17 (Box 87)
  - The Great Scout and Cat-House Thursday, 1975 November 26 (Box 87)
  - The Great Sioux Uprising, 1953 March 25 (Box 87)
  - The Great Sioux Uprising, trailer, 1953 April 10 (Box 87)
  - Great Son, 1948 February 9 (Box 87)
  - The Great Stagecoach Robbery, 1943 August 26 (Box 87)
  - The Great Stagecoach Robbery, 1944 August 22 (Box 87)
  - The Great Stagecoach Robbery, 1944 August 26 (Box 87)
  - The Grifters, 1989 September 30 (Box 87)
  - The Grifters, 1989 October 20 (Box 87)
  - The Groom Wore Spurs, 1959 November 10 (Box 87)
  - The Gulf, 1995 August 7 (Box 87)
  - The Gun and the Pulpit, 1974 January 23 (Box 87)
  - Gun Feud, 1946 April 27 (Box 87)
  - Gun for a Coward, 1956 March 13-28 (Box 87)
  - Gun Hand [Lawless Breed], 1952 April 10 (Box 87)
  - Gun Panic, [circa 1957] (Box 87)
  - Gun Panic, [circa 1957] (Box 87)
  - Gun Panic (Fanciest Dress in Madison Gulch), [circa 1957] (Box 87)
  - Gun Panic (The Marshall of Yellow Creek), [circa 1957] (Box 87)
  - Gun Point, 1955 (Box 88)
  - Gun Runner, [1949] (Box 88)
  - Gun Slinger, 1959 January 16 (Box 88)
  - A Gunfight, [1971] (Box 88)
  - Gunfight at Abilene, 1966 May 26 (Box 88)
  - Gunfight in Abilene, 1967 August 30 (Box 88)
  - Gunfight at Apache Wells [Duel at Apache Wells], 1956 May 1 (Box 88)
  - The Gunfighter and the Lady, 1993 (Box 88)
  - Gunfire, 1950 June 29 (Box 88)
  - The Gunhand [He Rides Tall], [circa 1963] (Box 88)
  - The Gunhand [He Rides Tall], 1964 (Box 88)
  - Gunman's Code, 1946 September16 (Box 88)
  - Gunman's Walk, 1957 October 11 (Box 139)
  - Guns and Guitars, [1936] (Box 88)
  - Guns in the Afternoon [Ride the High Country], 1961 September 14 (Box 137)
  - Guns of Rio Conchos, 1964 January 22 (Box 88)
  - The Gunsmith, 1962 January 10 (Box 88)
  - Hallelujah Train [Hallelujah Trail] [two copies], 7 February 1964; 2 (Box 88)
  - Hamster of Happiness, 1975 April 11 (Box 88)
  - The Hanged Man, 1973 October 22 (Box 88)
  - The Hanging Tree, 1958 March 28 (Box 88)
  - The Hanging Tree, 1958 April 17 (Box 88)
  - The Hanging Tree, 1958 May 12 (Box 88)
  - The Hanging Tree, 1958 June 10 (Box 88)
  - Hard Country [two copies], 1979 October 29; 2 (Box 88)
  - Hark, 1969 February 27 (Box 89)
  - Hark, 1970 February 5 (Box 89)
  - Harley Davidson and the Marlboro Man, 1990 April 23 (Box 89)
  - Harry and Tonto, [circa 1973] (Box 89)
  - The Haunted Mine, 1945 (Box 89)
  - Have Gun Will Travel, 1996 July 6 (Box 89)
  - Hawaii, 1965 January 21 (Box 89)
  - Hawaii, 1966 October 12 (Box 89)
  - Hawaii, 1966 October 31 (Box 89)
  - The Hawaiians, [circa 1964] (Box 89)
  - The Hawaiians, 1969 June 20 (Box 89)
  - He Rides Tall, 1963 October 25 (Box 89)
  - Heart of the Rio Grande, [1942] (Box 89)
  - Heart of the Rio Grande, 1942 January 7 (Box 89)
  - Hearts of the West, 1974 January 14 (Box 89)
  - Hearts of the West, 1974 July 22 (Box 89)
  - Heaven with a Gun, 1966 March 18 (Box 137)
  - Heck, 1971 October 12 (Box 89)
  - Hell Bent for Leather, 1959 December 1 (Box 89)
  - Hell Bent for Paradise, 1959 July 20 (Box 89)
  - The Hell Bent Kid [From Hell to Texas], 1957 September 6 (Box 90)
  - The Hell Bent Kid [From Hell to Texas], [1957] (Box 90)
  - The Hellfighters, 1968 February 27 (Box 90)
  - Hellfire [two copies], 1948 October 19; 2 (Box 90)
  - Her Beautiful Lady, [circa 1918] (Box 90)
  - Heroes of the Flame [chapters 1-12], [1931]; 15 (Box 90)
  - Heroes of the West [chapters 1-3], [1932] (Box 90)
  - Heroes of the West [chapters 4-7], [1932] (Box 90)
  - Heroes of the West [chapters 8-12], [1932] (Box 90)
  - Hey, I'm Alive, 1975 February 4 (Box 90)
  - Hi Gaucho, 1935 May 18 (Box 90)
  - Hi Gaucho, 1935 June 26 (Box 90)
  - Hi Lo Country, 1997 August 4 (Box 90)
  - Hiawatha, 1952 May 19 (Box 90)
  - High Noon, 1951 September 4 (Box 90)
  - High, Wide and Handsome, 1936 October 16 (Box 91)
  - High, Wide and Handsome, 1936 December 21 (Box 91)
  - High, Wide and Handsome, 1937 June 30 (Box 91)
  - High, Wide and Handsome, 1937 July 19 (Box 91)
  - High, Wide and Handsome, 1937 September 10 (Box 91)
  - Hitcher, 1984 December 17 (Box 91)
  - Hold High the Torch [Courage of Lassie], 1944 May 8 (Box 91)
  - Home From the Hill, 1958 May 5 (Box 91)
  - Home in Wyomin', undated (Box 91)
  - Home on the Prairie, [1939] (Box 91)
  - Home on the Range, 1934 December 5 (Box 91)
  - Hondo, 1953 May 1 (Box 91)
  - The Honkers, 1971 December 21 (Box 91)
  - The Honkers, 1971 April 19 (Box 91)
  - Honky-Tonk, 1974 February 4 (Box 91)
  - Honor of the West, 1941 July 2 (Box 91)
  - Hope Floats, 1997 January 14 (Box 91)
  - Horizons West, 1952 July 9 (Box 91)
  - Hour of the Gun, 1967 July 28 (Box 91)
  - How the West Was Won, 1977; 2 (Box 91)
    Includes part six and part nine.
  - The Hunters, 1974 March 29 (Box 91)
  - The Hunting Party, 1969 May 27 (Box 91)
  - The Hunting Party, 1970 May 26 (Box 91)
  - I Shot Billy the Kid, 1950 July 13 (Box 92)
  - In Old California, 1942 (Box 92)
  - In Old Missouri, 1940 February 21 (Box 92)
  - In Old Wyoming, 1944 Mar 23 (Box 92)
  - Incendiary Blonde, 1943 October 8 (Box 92)
  - Incident at Phantom Hill, 1965 July 2 (Box 92)
  - Inferno, 1953 February 7 (Box 92)
  - The Innocents, undated (Box 92)
  - Iron Horse [There Isn't a Train I Wouldn't Take], 1965 September 7 (Box 92)
  - Iron Horse [There Isn't a Train I Wouldn't Take], 1965 November 4 (Box 92)
  - The Iroquois Trail, 1950 January 10 (Box 92)
  - Ishi, 1991 September 30 (Box 92)
  - Island Sons, 1986 January 30 (Box 92)
  - [Jamboree], 1943 December 22 (Box 92)
  - The James Family, 1974 October 10 (Box 92)
  - Jaws of Justice, 1933 (Box 92)
  - Jesse James, 1938 June 1 (Box 92)
  - Jessie, 1984 March 1 (Box 92)
  - Jim Tracker and the Valley of Gold [The Gold Rush Family], undated (Box 93)
  - Joe Dakota, 1957 March 22 (Box 93)
  - The Jones Family at the Grand Canyon [Quick Millions], 1939 March 31 (Box 93)
  - Journey to Shiloh, 1966 July 13 (Box 93)
  - Journey to Shiloh, 1967 July 11 (Box 93)
  - Juarez, 1938 October 29 (Box 93)
  - Jubal Troop, 1944 September 13 (Box 93)
  - Jubilee Trail, 1952 January 4 (Box 93)
  - Justice Delayed, 1985 December 11 (Box 93)
  - Kalifornia, [circa 1992] (Box 93)
  - Kalifornia, 1992 January 10 (Box 93)
  - Kansas, 1987 March 1 (Box 93)
  - The Kansas Raiders [The Black Flag], 1950 May 9 (Box 93)
  - Kansas Raiders, 1950 October 30 (Box 93)
  - Kenny Rogers as The Gambler, 1979 October 16 (Box 93)
  - The Kid, 1988 September 19 (Box 93)
  - The Kid Came West [West of the El Dorado], 1949 (Box 93)
  - The Killers, 1964 April 13 (Box 93)
  - The Killing of a Chinese Bookie, 1975 June (Box 93)
  - King of the Grizzlies, 1969 November (Box 94)
  - King of the Texas Rangers, 1941 (Box 94)
  - King of the Texas Rangers, 1941 May 28 (Box 94)
  - The King of Wild Horses, 1924 (Box 94)
  - The Kiowa War-Wagon, [1967] (Box 94)
  - Kiss of Fire, 1955 March 18 (Box 94)
  - Klondike Annie, 1936 February 15 (Box 94)
  - Knightrider Twenty-Ten, 1993 February 6 (Box 94)
  - Knightrider Twenty-Ten, 1993 Febrary 16 (Box 94)
  - Kona Coast, 1967 January 2 (Box 94)
  - Kona Coast, 1967 June 29 (Box 94)
  - Kung Fu: The Movie, 1985 July 29 (Box 94)
  - Kung Fu: The Movie, 1985 August 23 (Box 94)
  - L.A. Confidential, 1996 February 12 (Box 95)
  - L. A. Story, 1990 March 21 (Box 95)
  - Labrava, undated (Box 95)
  - The Lady from Cheyenne, 1941 March 18 (Box 95)
  - The Lady Gambles, 1949 March 3 (Box 95)
  - Lady in a Jam, 1942 Jun 18 (Box 95)
  - Lake of Fire, [circa 1957] (Box 95)
  - Lake of Fire, [1957] (Box 95)
  - The Land that Touches Mine, [circa 1955?] (Box 95)
  - Lantern in Her Hand, 1994 October 28 (Box 95)
  - The Last Frontier Uprising, 1946 May 23 (Box 95)
  - Last Gun, 1976 (Box 95)
  - The Last Gunfighter, 1969 February 7 (Box 95)
  - The Last Hard Man, 1975 September 26 (Box 95)
  - The Last of the Comancheros, undated (Box 95)
  - The Last of the Duanes, 1930 April 19 (Box 96)
  - The Last of the Duanes, 1941 March 31 (Box 96)
  - The Last of the Fast Guns, 1958 March 24 (Box 96)
  - Last of the Mohicans, 1991 March 19 (Box 96)
  - Last of the Wild Horses, 1952 March 6 (Box 96)
  - The Last Outpost, [1951] (Box 96)
  - The Last Picture Show, 1970 October 2 (Box 96)
  - The Last Stand, [1938] (Box 96)
  - The Last Sunset, [1961] (Box 96)
  - The Last Wagon, 1956 January 12 (Box 96)
  - Latigo [Support Your Local Gunfighter], [1971] (Box 96)
  - Law and Order, 1952 January 3 (Box 96)
  - Law and Order, 1953 January 28 (Box 96)
  - Law Man, 1954 November 16 (Box 96)
  - Law Man, 1955 July 11 (Box 96)
  - Law Man [Star in the Dust], 1955 July 28 (Box 96)
  - Lawful Outlaws [Range War], 1939 March 30 (Box 96)
  - Lawless Code [two copies], 1949 July; 2 (Box 96)
  - LBJ, 1985 November 25 (Box 96)
  - Leadbelly, 1974 (Box 96)
  - The Leatherstocking Saga, undated (Box 96)
  - The Left Handed Gun, 1957 (Box 139)
  - Legend at Sundown [Standing Tall], 1977 Ocober 3 (Box 97)
  - Legend of Billie Jean, 1984 March (Box 97)
  - The Legend of Chuck-a-Luck [Rancho Notorious], [1952] (Box 97)
  - The Legend of Evil Roy Slade, 1971 October 11 (Box 97)
  - Legend of Lylah Clare, 1967 Jun 26 (Box 137)
  - The Legend of the Boy and the Eagle, 1967 May (Box 97)
  - The Legend of the Lone Ranger, 1979 July 3 (Box 97)
  - The Legend of Zorro, 1994 July 6 (Box 97)
  - Legends of the Fall, 1993 March 16 (Box 97)
  - Lewis & Clark, 1994 (Box 139)
    Pilot and treatments for a six-hour miniseries.
  - The Lightfootes, 1975 February 25 (Box 97)
  - Lightning Jack, 1993 May 28 (Box 97)
  - Little Big Horn, 1950 November 27 (Box 97)
  - Little Big Horn, 1951 May 12 (Box 97)
  - Little Big Man, 1969 April 4 (Box 97)
  - The Live Wire [The Right Approach], 1960 October 6 (Box 97)
  - The Llano Kid, 1939 November 6 (Box 97)
  - Lone Cowboy, 1933 November 1 (Box 97)
  - The Lone Hand, 1952 December 22 (Box 97)
  - The Lone Ranger, [circa 1953] (Box 97)
  - The Lone Ranger Rides Again, 1939; 7 (Box 139)
  - The Lone Ranger Rides Again, 1939; 8 (Box 140)
  - The Lone Rider Rides On, [1941] (Box 97)
  - Lone Star, 1995 January 2 (Box 97)
  - Lone Star, 1995 April 4 (Box 97)
  - Lone Star, [1995] (Box 97)
  - Lone Star Raiders, 1940 October 28 (Box 97)
  - The Lone Star Ranger, 1941 August 6 (Box 97)
  - Lone Star Trail, 1942 September 9 (Box 98)
  - Lone Star Trail, 1942 November 3 (Box 98)
  - Lone Star Trail, 1942 December 14 (Box 98)
  - Lone Texas Ranger, 1944 October 12 (Box 98)
  - Lonely Man, 1956 October 22 (Box 98)
  - Lonesome Dove, [1988]; 6 (Box 98)
  - The Lonesome Gun, 1956 August 31 (Box 98)
  - Lonesome Trail, 1945 August 31 (Box 98)
  - Lonesome Trail, 1955 May 18 (Box 98)
  - The Long Gun, 1967 July 20 (Box 98)
  - The Long Ride Home [two copies], 1965 July 12; 2 (Box 98)
  - The Long Ride Home [two copies], 1965 September 8; 2 (Box 98)
  - The Longhorn, 1951 (Box 98)
  - Longriders, 1979 June 6 (Box 98)
  - Longriders, 1979 June 28 (Box 98)
  - The Looters, 1954 May 8 (Box 98)
  - The Lost Wagon Train, [circa 1936] (Box 98)
  - Lucky Cisco Kid [Cisco Kid #3], 1940 February 20 (Box 98)
  - Lucky Lady, 1974 November 18 (Box 99)
  - The Magnificent Seven Ride!, [1972] (Box 99)
  - The Magnificent Seven Ride!, 1972 May 2 (Box 99)
  - Make Haste to Live, 1953 September 14 (Box 99)
  - Man Called Gannon, 1967 October 12 (Box 99)
  - A Man Called Horse [two copies], 1968 September 26; 2 (Box 99)
  - Man Called Horse, [1968]; 2 (Box 99)
    Includes photograph and initial story treatment.
  - Man Called Horse [director's shooting script], 1968 September 26 (Box 99)
  - The Man from Abilene, 1956 September 11 (Box 99)
  - The Man from Bitter Ridge, 1955 February 8 (Box 99)
  - Man from Montana [two copies], 1941 March 19; 2 (Box 99)
  - Man from Montana, 1941 July 25 (Box 99)
  - Man from Music Mountain, [1938] (Box 99)
  - The Man from Oklahoma, 1945 February 27 (Box 99)
  - Man from Rainbow Valley, 1946 February 2 (Box 99)
  - Man from Rio Grande, 1943 July 22 (Box 99)
  - [The Man from Thunder River], 1943 March 4 (Box 99)
  - The Man in the Saddle, 1928 January 20 (Box 99)
  - Man in the Shadow, 1957 November 12 (Box 99)
  - Man in the Wilderness, 1971 February 4 (Box 100)
  - Man Power, 1941 March 4 (Box 100)
  - The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing, 1972 June (Box 100)
  - The Man Who Loved Cat Dancing, 1973 January 17 (Box 100)
  - The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance, undated (Box 100)
  - Man Without a Star, 1954 January 29 (Box 100)
  - Man Without a Star, 1955 January 19 (Box 100)
  - Marauder, 1968 March 26 (Box 100)
  - Marauders, 1954 August 13 (Box 137)
  - Marina's Story, 1991 April 3 (Box 100)
  - Marina's Story, 1991 August 18 (Box 100)
  - Mark of the Apache [Tomahawk Trail], 1956 May 9 (Box 100)
  - The Mark of the Renegade, 1951 March 19 (Box 100)
  - The Mark of Zorro, 1974 June 4 (Box 100)
  - Marshal of Amarillo, 1947 August 5 (Box 100)
  - Marshal of Gunsmoke, 1943 (Box 100)
  - Marshal of Heldorado, 1950 March 14 (Box 100)
  - Marshal of Laredo, 1945 February 9 (Box 100)
  - The Mask of Zorro, 1996 September 27 (Box 100)
  - The Mask of Zorro, 1996 December 18 (Box 100)
  - Masked Caballero [The Masked Rider], 1941 May 28 (Box 100)
  - Maverick, undated (Box 100)
  - Maverick, 1993 August 16 (Box 100)
  - The Maverick Queen, 1955 July 20 (Box 100)
  - McCabe and Mrs. Miller, 1969 April 4 (Box 101)
  - McLintock!, 1963 July 31 (Box 101)
  - Meal Ticket [This Is the Life], 1935 July 6 (Box 101)
  - Medicine Show, 1993 June 29 (Box 101)
  - Medico of Painted Springs, 1941 April 14 (Box 137)
  - Melody Range [Oklahoma Blues], [1948] (Box 101)
  - Melody Trail, [1935] (Box 101)
  - Melody Trail, [1935] (Box 101)
  - Melody Trail, 1935 September 21 (Box 101)
  - Melvin and Howard [two copies], 1978 November 29; 2 (Box 101)
  - Men of Texas, 1942 June 25 (Box 101)
  - Men of the Timberland, 1941 May 23 (Box 101)
  - Mexicali Rose, [1939] (Box 101)
  - Michener Project [Dynasty], 1975 June 19 (Box 101)
  - Mickey, 1984 October 8 (Box 101)
  - The Missing, 2003 April 9 (Box 101)
  - The Model Shop, 1968 April 18 (Box 101)
  - Money, Women and Guns, 1958 March 23 (Box 101)
  - Money, Women and Guns, 1958 May 28 (Box 101)
  - The Monkey Wrench Gang, 1978 May (Box 101)
  - Montana, 1980 (Box 101)
  - More Dead Than Alive, 1968 April 24 (Box 101)
  - More Dead Than Alive, 1969 (Box 101)
  - Mountain King, 1987 January 30 (Box 101)
  - Mountain Rhythm, [1939] (Box 101)
  - Mr. Horn, 1978 May 26 (Box 102)
  - Mulholland Falls, 1993 August 13 (Box 102)
  - Mulholland Falls, 1994 July 28 (Box 102)
  - Mustang Country, 1975 January 30 (Box 102)
  - My American Wife, 1936 July 18 (Box 102)
  - My Friend Flicka, 1942 June 6 (Box 102)
  - My Reminiscences as a Cowboy Cowboy, 1930 (Box 102)
  - The Mysterious Rider, 1933 January 11 (Box 102)
  - The Mysterious Rider, 1938 September 19 (Box 102)
  - Na-Ko-Ma, King of the Stallions, June 11, 1942 (Box 102)
  - Na-Ko-Ma, King of the Stallions, [1942] (Box 102)
  - Natural Born Killers, 1992 February 1 (Box 102)
  - Navajo Joe, 1967 October 19 (Box 102)
  - Nevada, 1930 September 20 (Box 102)
  - Nevada, 1935 November 6 (Box 102)
  - Nevada Smith, 1965 June 30 (Box 102)
  - Nevada Smith, 1966 April 15 (Box 102)
  - Nevada Trail, 1949 June 23 (Box 102)
  - The New Daughters of Joshua Cabe, 1976 January 9 (Box 102)
  - The New Adventures of Wee Willie Winkie, undated (Box 102)
  - The New Maverick, 1978 March 16 (Box 103)
  - The Newton Boys, 1997 April 15 (Box 103)
  - Nickelodeon, 1975 December 8 (Box 103)
  - The Night Doc Holliday Stayed Sober, undated (Box 103)
  - A Night in Old Mexico, 1994 December 11 (Box 103)
  - The Night of the Tiger [Ride Beyond Vengeance], 1965 May 10 (Box 103)
  - Nightbreaker, 1988 October 14 (Box 103)
  - No Name on the Bullet, 1958 December 3 (Box 103)
  - Nobody Lives Forever, 1944 July 11 (Box 140)
  - Nobody Loves a Drunken Indian, 1969 March 26 (Box 103)
  - Nobody Loves Flapping Eagle, 1969 June 24 (Box 103)
  - North of 36 [Conquering Horde], 1930 September 30 (Box 103)
  - North to the Klondike, 1942 January 13 (Box 103)
  - North to Yesterday, 1969 January 20 (Box 103)
  - North West Mounted Police, 1939 November 11 (Box 103)
  - North West Mounted Police, 1939 November 29 (Box 103)
  - North West Mounted Police, 1940 February 13 (Box 103)
  - North West Mounted Police, undated (Box 103)
  - Northwest Frontier, 1966 August 10 (Box 103)
  - Northwest Trail, [1945] (Box 103)
  - Now I'm a Lady [Goin' to Town], 1934 December 17 (Box 103)
  - O Pioneers, 1991 May 1 (Box 104)
  - O'Brien #6 [Fighting Gringo], 1939 July 5 (Box 104)
  - Oh, Susanna, [1936] (Box 104)
  - The Oklahoma City Dolls, 1980 June 5 (Box 104)
  - Oklahoma Crude, 1972 March 3 (Box 104)
  - Oklahoma Renegades, 13 June 1940 (Box 104)
  - Old Chisholm Trail, 1942 July 20 (Box 104)
  - The Old Corral, [1936] (Box 104)
  - Once Upon a Horse, [1958] (Box 104)
  - Once Upon a Horse, 1957 July 5 (Box 104)
  - Once Upon a Texas Train, 1987 August 7 (Box 104)
  - The One and Only, Genuine, Original Family Band, 1966 December 12 (Box 104)
  - One From the Heart, [circa 1981] (Box 104)
  - One Little Indian, 1973 May (Box 104)
  - The Onion Field, 1978 November 17 (Box 104)
  - Only the Valiant, 1950 March 23 (Box 104)
  - The Oregon Trail, 1975 July 21 (Box 104)
  - The Oregon Trail, 1975 August 14 (Box 104)
  - The Oregon Trail, [circa 1975] (Box 104)
  - The Oregon Trail, 1976 January 10 (Box 104)
  - The Oregon Trail, trailer, 1939 April 26 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 1: The Renegade's Revenge], 1939 April 13 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 2: The Flaming Forest], 1939 Apr 14 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 3: The Brink of Disaster], 1939 April 15 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 4: Thundering Doom], 1939 April 27 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 5: The Menacing Herd], 1939 April 28 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 6: Indian Vengeance], 1939 May 3 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 7: Trail of Treachery], 1939 May 11 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 8: Redskin's Revenge], 1939 May 15 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 9: The Avalanche of Doom], undated (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 10: The Plunge of Peril], 1939 June 1 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 11: Trapped by the Flames], 1939 June 2 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 12: The Baited Trap], 1939 June 5 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 13: Crashing Timber], 1939 June 13 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 14: Death in the Night], 1939 June 14 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail [Chapter 15: Trail's End], 1939 June 15 (Box 105)
  - Oregon Trail Scouts, 1946 August 13 (Box 105)
  - Origin of the Crown Dance, 1984 August 1 (Box 105)
  - Outland, 1979-1980 (Box 105)
  - Outlaw, 1986 April 28 (Box 105)
  - Outlaw Blues, 1976 January 21 (Box 105)
  - The Outlaw Josey Wales, 1975 September 10 (Box 105)
  - Outlaws of the Cherokee Trail, 1941 July 18 (Box 105)
  - Outlaws of the Cherokee Trail, [1941] (Box 105)
  - Outlaw Trail, 1946 June 8 (Box 106)
  - Outlaw Women, [1952] (Box 106)
  - Outlaw Women, [circa 1952] (Box 106)
  - Outside Man, 1972 February 5 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter One], 1941 August 5 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Two], 1941 July 28 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Three], 1941 July 28 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Four], 1941 July 28 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [ Chapter Five], 1941 July 29 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Six], 1941 July 29 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Seven], 1941 July 29 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Eight], 1941 July 29 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Ten], 1941 July 31 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Eleven], 1941 August 1 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Twelve], 1941 August 4 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Thirteen], 1941 August 4 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Fourteen], 1941 August 2 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail [Chapter Fifteen], 1941 August 4 (Box 106)
  - Overland Mail Robbery, 1943 August 26 (Box 106)
  - Ox-Bow Incident, 1942 June 3 (Box 106)
  - Paint Your Wagon, 1968 May 16 (Box 107)
  - Painted Desert, 1938 June 1 (Box 107)
  - Painted Desert, 1938 June 2 (Box 107)
  - The Painted Hills, 1950 January 4 (Box 107)
  - The Painted Stallion, 1937 (Box 107)
  - The Paleface, 1947 July 8 (Box 107)
  - The Paleface, 1948 April 6 (Box 107)
  - Pals of the Pecos [two copies], 21 February 1941; 2 (Box 107)
  - Pals of the Saddle, 1938 July 9 (Box 107)
  - Pardners, 1955 November 18 (Box 107)
  - The Parson of the Panamint, 1941 June 25 (Box 107)
  - Partners of the Sunset, [1948] (Box 107)
  - Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid, 1972 October 18 (Box 140)
  - Pat Garrett and Billy the Kid, 1972 November 7 (Box 107)
  - Pawnee, 1956 September 6 (Box 140)
  - Peace With Honor, undated (Box 107)
  - The Pecos Kid, 1940 February 14 (Box 107)
  - Penelope, 1965 June 15 (Box 107)
  - Penelope, 1966 May 16 (Box 107)
  - Perils of the Yukon [chapters 3-15], 1922; 13 (Box 108)
  - Peter Lundy and the Medicine Hat Stallion, 1977 May 24 (Box 108)
  - Peter Lundy and the Medicine Hat Stallion [Broken Chain], 1977 December 6 (Box 108)
  - Petulia, 1967 March 17 (Box 138)
  - Phantom Plainsmen, 1942 April 23 (Box 108)
  - Phantom Rider, undated (Box 108)
  - Phantom Rider's Revenge [The Old Frontier], 1949 November 22 (Box 108)
  - The Piano Sport, 1967 December 25 (Box 108)
  - Pilgrim, [circa 1978] (Box 108)
  - Pillars of the Sky, 1953 November 13 (Box 108)
  - Pillars of the Sky, 1956 January 27 (Box 108)
  - Pioneer Marshal, [1950] (Box 108)
  - Pioneer Woman, 1973 August 14 (Box 108)
  - Pioneers, 1940 (Box 108)
  - Pirates of Monterey, 1946 March 4 (Box 108)
  - Pirates of Monterey, 1947 October 27 (Box 108)
  - Pistol Harvest, 1950 November 2 (Box 108)
  - The Plainsman, 1936 May 28 (Box 109)
  - The Plainsman, 1936 July 14 (Box 109)
  - The Plainsman, 1936 October 21 (Box 109)
  - The Plainsman, 1936 December 8 (Box 109)
  - The Plainsman, 1965 August 26 (Box 109)
  - Play Misty for Me, 1968 July 17 (Box 109)
  - Pocket Money, 1971 April 26 (Box 109)
  - Poker Alice, [circa 1986] (Box 109)
  - Poker Alice, 1987 January 19 (Box 109)
  - The Pony Express, 1952 May 21 (Box 109)
  - Pony Express Days, 1938 (Box 109)
  - Pony Post, 1940 September 10 (Box 109)
  - Positively True Adventures of the Alleged Texas Cheerleader-Murdering Mom, 1992 June 17 (Box 109)
  - Posse, 1974 August 6 (Box 109)
  - Posse, 1992 August 12 (Box 109)
  - Posse From Hell, 1961 February 20 (Box 109)
  - Posse from Hell [Magnificent Seven Ride], 1971 March 1 (Box 109)
  - The Postman Always Rings Twice, 1981 (Box 110)
  - Powderkeg, [circa 1950- 1960] (Box 110)
  - Prairie Madness [cover title: Wagon Train], 1969 Nov 25 (Box 137)
  - Prairie Moon, [1938] (Box 110)
  - Prairie Pioneers, 27 November 1940 (Box 110)
  - Prairie Pirates, 1945 April 9 (Box 110)
  - Prairie Pirates, 1948 November 18 (Box 110)
  - Presbyterian Church Wager [McCabe and Miller], 1971 January 19 (Box 110)
  - Pride of the Plains [two copies], 1943 September 24; 2 (Box 110)